Welcome to the Theatre of the Absurd.
The Theatre Bizarre is a horror film directed by Tom Savini.
Down a seedy city street in her neighborhood, young Enola Penny is
obsessed with what appears to be a long abandoned theatre.
One night, she sees that the front door is slightly ajar
and impulsively decides to sneak inside.
But there in the dark, decrepit auditorium, a show
unlike any other unfolds before her eyes.
Its host is an eerie human puppet named Peg Poett who will introduce Penny to six tales of the bizarre: A couple traveling in a remote part of the French Pyrenees cross paths with a lustful witch; A paranoid lover faces the wrath of a partner who has been pushed to her limit; The Freudian dreams of an unfaithful husband
blur the lines between fantasy and reality; The horrors of the real world are interpreted through the mind of a child; A woman addicted to other people's memories gets her fix through the vitreous fluid of her victims' eyeballs; And a perverse obsession with sweets turns sour for a couple in too deep.
Peg Poett, played by Udo Kier.
Enola Penny, played by Virginia Newcomb.
Squalid Woman, played by Amanda Marquardt.
Gypsy, played by Amelia M. Gotham.
Mere Antoinette, played by Catriona MacColl.
Martin, played by Shane Woodward.
The Theatre Bizarre is a 2011 American horror anthology film.
The six segments are directed by Douglas Buck, Buddy Giovinazzo, David
Gregory, Karim Hussain, Tom Savini and Richard Stanley.
The wraparound segments featuring Udo Kier were directed by Jeremy Kasten.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.